{
  "GroupId": 5,
  "GroupName": "INDIA",
  "Levels": [
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 1,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "INTERNSHIP",
          "question": "Temporary job for gaining experience in a field"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "HEARTBREAK",
          "question": "Emotional pain from the end of a relationship"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "OBJECTIVES",
          "question": "Goals or targets aimed for in a project"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "TERMINATOR",
          "question": "Iconic cyborg from Arnold Schwarzenegger's famous film"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "BREAKDANCE",
          "question": "Street dance style with spinning and acrobatic moves"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "DISHWASHER",
          "question": "Appliance used to clean dishes automatically"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "ATTACHMENT",
          "question": "Additional part or document added to something"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "COLLECTORS",
          "question": "People who gather and preserve items of interest"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "TAJ MAHAL",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 2,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "DELAWARE",
          "question": "First state to join the United States Union"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "ILLUSION",
          "question": "Magic trick that tricks the eye"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "WINDMILL",
          "question": "Large structure with blades, featured in 'Don Quixote'"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "ATHLETIC",
          "question": "Active and strong in sports"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "LEMONADE",
          "question": "A sweet drink made from lemons"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "IMPOSTER",
          "question": "Someone pretending to be someone else"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "OFFTRACK",
          "question": "Not following the intended path"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "DELIVERY",
          "question": "Service for bringing packages to your door"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ISLANDER",
          "question": "Someone who lives on an island"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "STALLION",
          "question": "Large, strong horse often used in racing"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "DIVIDEND",
          "question": "Part of a company's profit shared with shareholders"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "OVERCAST",
          "question": "Cloudy sky without visible sun"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BALSAMIC",
          "question": "Vinegar type, often used in salads."
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BLACKOUT",
          "question": "Complete power loss or a sudden memory lapse"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "DIWALI FESTIVAL",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 3,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "GAMBLER",
          "question": "Person who takes risks with money, often in casinos"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "PREVIEW",
          "question": "Glimpse of something before its official release or showing"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "MANAGER",
          "question": "Person overseeing employees and operations"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "HYGIENE",
          "question": "Set of practices performed to preserve health"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CHANNEL",
          "question": "Broadcast platform for TV or radio content"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "GOODBYE",
          "question": "Common farewell expression"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "NOODLES",
          "question": "Long, thin pasta often used in Asian dishes"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "LAWSUIT",
          "question": "Legal action taken in court"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "NUGGETS",
          "question": "Popular chicken item at McDonald's"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "MEN IN BLUE",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 4,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CLUMSY",
          "question": "Always dropping things or tripping over own feet"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CANADA",
          "question": "Country known for its maple syrup and hockey"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "LYCHEE",
          "question": "Tropical fruit often used in desserts and drinks"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "GARAGE",
          "question": "Place to park your car or store tools"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "EASTER",
          "question": "Holiday with egg hunts and chocolate bunnies"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "HERMES",
          "question": "Luxury fashion brand known for its iconic handbags"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "ERRAND",
          "question": "Task you might run around town to complete"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "SAVAGE",
          "question": "Term for someone or something fierce and untamed"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "BETRAY",
          "question": "To break trust or loyalty with someone"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "BUYING",
          "question": "Acquiring items or services through purchase"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "BLONDE",
          "question": "Hair color often associated with light shades"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "THIGHS",
          "question": "Upper parts of your leg, between the hip and knee"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "TENNIS",
          "question": "Sport where players hit a ball over a net with rackets"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "MAHATMA GANDHI",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 5,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "NEIGHBORHOOD",
          "question": "Residential area where people live close to each other"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "BILLIONAIRES",
          "question": "People with wealth exceeding one billion dollars"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "INTELLIGENCE",
          "question": "High level of mental ability, often linked to problem-solving and learning"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "LEGISLATIONS",
          "question": "Laws and rules established by government authorities"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "AERODYNAMICS",
          "question": "Study of how air interacts with moving objects"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "ACKNOWLEDGED",
          "question": "Officially recognized or accepted after careful review"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "PSYCHOLOGIST",
          "question": "Professional who studies the human mind and behavior"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "TECHNOPHOBIA",
          "question": "Fear or dislike of advanced technology and gadgets"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 6,
          "answer_text": "JURISDICTION",
          "question": "Power to enforce laws and manage legal disputes within a specific area"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}